http://www.kirkusreviews.com/legal/privacy/

Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Kirkus.com or any Kirkus Media LLC digital properties, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy notice.
Information Collection
When you visit the site, we collect basic information that does not identify individual users, including the pages visited. We then aggregate this information with thousands of other pieces of information to improve our site and make your time on the site as valuable and efficient as possible.
We will not rent or sell your name, email address or personal information to any third party without your permission. However, we must cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer. We do reserve the right to send emails on behalf of our partners and affiliates
The amount and type of information that Kirkus Media LLC gathers and stores depends on the nature of the interaction. To provide an optimal user experience, Kirkus Media LLC may need to securely pass user information to affiliated third-party organizations (example, Facebook). Kirkus Media LLC thoroughly vets each and every affiliated organization's privacy policies to ensure they comply with the same high standards as Kirkus Media LLC.
Information We Need
When you order subscriptions, products, or services, we need to know your name, email address, shipping address, billing address, phone number, and credit card number with expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. We do not store your credit card information in our database and have no access to it after processing your subscription. We ask for your phone number in the event that our customer service representatives or delivery services need to contact you about your order.
We store all files uploaded for author services (example, manuscripts), personal information (example, email addresses), and project information (example, book titles) on a secure server and restrict access to only the professionals contracted to work on your project and key Kirkus personnel. Contracted professionals are required to sign non-disclosure agreements prior to working on any Kirkus projects.
Changing Your Information
If at any time you would like to change any information in your account, just click the Log In or My Account link. Here you can update your password, contact information, and email preferences. Be sure to click the Submit button at the bottom when you have updated your account.
To remove your name from our email list, please click on the link located at the bottom of each email or edit your email option in your account.
If you would like to delete your personally identifying information from Kirkus Media LLC, you may do so by emailing the request to customercare@kirkus.com. Without the request of deletion, you give Kirkus Media LLC explicit consent to retain your personally identifying data indefinitely.
Our policy is intended to provide you with the safest and most secure user experience possible. Since the law, offerings and technologies change, we reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of our privacy policy at any time without prior notice. If you have further questions, please feel free to contact our Customer Service team at 800-316-9361.
The Magazine: Kirkus Reviews
The 100 best nonfiction and 100 best YA books of the year, plus our regular December 1 issue.
subscribe
The Kirkus Star
One of the most coveted designations in the book industry, the Kirkus Star marks books of exceptional merit.
The Kirkus Prize
The Kirkus Prize is among the richest literary awards in America, awarding $50,000 in three categories annually.
See the 2020 winners.
Great Books & News Curated For You
Be the first to read books news and see reviews, news and features in
Kirkus Reviews. Get awesome content delivered to your inbox every week.
Thank you!
EMAIL ADDRESS
SIGN UP
Discover Books Children'sFictionMystery & ThrillerTeenScience Fiction & FantasyNonfictionRomanceBiography & Memoir
News & Features BestsellersBook ListsProfilesPerspectivesBook to ScreenKirkus TV videosFully Booked PodcastIn the NewsAwardsSeen & Heard
Kirkus Prize Winners & FinalistsAbout the Kirkus PrizeKirkus Prize Judges
Magazine Current IssueAll IssuesManage My SubscriptionSubscribe
Writers’ Center Hire a Professional Book EditorGet Your Book ReviewedLaunch a Pro Connect Author PagePromote Your BookLearn About The Book Industry
More Diversity CollectionsPro ConnectMy Account/Login
About Kirkus HistoryOur TeamContestsFAQPress CenterCareersContact usPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsReprints, Permission &
Excerpting PolicyContact UsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsReprints, Permission & Excerpting Policy© Copyright 2020 Kirkus Media LLC. All Rights Reserved.Follow×CloseWe can’t wait for you to join Kirkus!Please sign up to continue.It’s free and takes less than 10 seconds!Already have an account? Log in.
OR
Sign in with Google
Trouble signing in?
Retrieve credentials.
×CloseAlmost there!×CloseWelcome Back!Sign in using your Kirkus account
OR
Sign in with Google
Trouble signing in?
Retrieve credentials.
Need Help?Contact us: 1-800-316-9361 or email
customercare@kirkus.com×CloseDon’t fret. We’ll find you.Choose OneNeed Help?Contact us: 1-800-316-9361 or email
customercare@kirkus.com×CloseHey there, book lover.We’re glad you found a book that interests you!Please select an existing bookshelf
